Critical illness insurance can sometimes be a
headache.  I have to check the list of diseases
first and then I'm confused about whether this can be claimed or
not?  When facing uncertainty,
FD Insurance provides easy-to
-understand solutions.  Get to know FWD Critical First
Protection.  Insurance that focuses on the
consequences of critical illness conditions, not the
type of illness.  Even rare critical conditions that are
not yet commonly known or
have not yet been discovered can still be covered
as long as they meet the specified criteria
.  Starting from the initial stage, you
can claim with affordable premiums
, you can get
insurance money of up to 200%.  This freedom is
yours.  Choose a protection period that
suits your life expectancy up to the age of 65, 75, 85,
or even 100 years.  Since the claim for 50% of
the meeting money is approved, you no longer
need to pay the premium.  If you are healthy
until the end of the insurance period, 100% of the premium
can be returned to you.  Life more certain
and worry-free?  Immediately contact your
nearest FWD insurance.
FWD Critical First Protection.  Enjoy a
quality life.
[Music]